♪ In the not-too-distant
future ♪
♪ way down in deep 13 ♪
♪ dr. Forrester
and tv's frank ♪
♪ were hatching
an evil scheme ♪
♪ they hired a temp
by the name of mike ♪
♪ just a regular joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ their experiment
needed a good test case ♪
♪ so they conked him
on the noggin ♪
♪ and they shot him into space ♪
Get me down!
♪ We'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
- ♪ the worst we can find ♪
- ♪ la-la-la ♪
♪ he'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
- ♪ and we'll monitor his mind ♪
- ♪ la-la-la ♪
♪ now, keep in mind
mike can't control ♪
- ♪ where the movies
begin or end ♪
- ♪ la-la-la ♪
♪ he'll try
to keep his sanity ♪
♪ with the help
of his robot friends ♪
♪ robot roll call ♪
- Cambot!
- Show yourself.
I'm not ready.
Hello there.
That's one "o".
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes ♪
- ♪ and other science facts ♪
- ♪ la-la-la ♪
♪ just repeat to yourself,
"it's just a show ♪
♪ "I should
really just relax ♪
♪ for mystery science
theater 3000" ♪
Hi, everyone. Welcome
to the satellite of love.
I'm mike. And you're just
in time for the final dress
and tech rehearsal
for love letters,
starting crow t. Robot--
- hello.
- ...And tom servo.
- Hello.
- You know, love letters
is a lot like
same time, next year,
only you don't have to
remember any lines.
- Ready, guys?
- Yes. Ready.
And... anytime.
"Dear melissa,
hi, how are you?
I am fine.
"Remember when
we met at college last year
and fell in love?
Sincerely, andrew."
"Dear andrew,
I read your letter today
"and was overcome
with love for you.
"By the way,
I have married steven,
"but we'll probably grow apart.
More later, melissa."
"Dear melissa, that's okay.
I got married too.
But I totally love you,
andrew."
"Dear andrew,
I'm having steven's baby,
"but I wanted to let you know
that it's you that I love.
Take care, melissa."
"Dear melissa,
I turned middle-aged this week.
"I'm a rich wasp,
and I love you.
All my best, andrew."
"Dear andrew,
I'm a grandmother now.
"Steven and I
have grown apart.
"Go figure.
I do so love you.
Stay well, melissa."
"Dear melissa, my children
have reproduced also.
"Our love endures
through the years, huh?
Boy, do you I love you.
Regards, andrew."
- [Clapping]
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.
- That was fantastic.
Bravo and brava.
- Really?
I saw stephanie zimbalist, jr.
and chris lemmon do that,
and they did not do it justice
compared to you two gentlemen.
- Servo there
was setting the line.
- No, no. It's crow. Crow--
well, theater is a group thing,
and you were able
to hold moments--
- moment by moment is what
theater is all about.
- There was a moment.
It was a very ephemeral thing,
and it was almost not there.
But it was there.
Mm. You know, servo, crow,
I'm not just a friend of yours,
I'm a fan.
Oh, hey, ruth gordon
and garson kanin are calling.
- Oh.
- Don't stop touching me.
Uh, we're not ready.
You go first.
Hey, no problem.
Our invention is you.
- I'm dr. Clayton forrester.
- And I'm tv's frank.
- See?
- [Snickering]
Cute. But I don't
quite understand the--
I'm dr. Clayton forrester,
the one with the weak chin.
I'm going to hit tv's frank
because of my deep resentment
at my own limitations.
I'm tv's frank,
and I'm going to take it,
because I have
no self-confidence.
- Ow, ow, ow!
- [Laughter]
Well, you do have
kind of a weak chin.
Forget the chin, frank.
Don't you see what's happening?
We're losing their respect.
It's all on the line here, man.
We've gotta do something,
and fast!
Hey, we're just funning ya.
Shall I hit you again,
tv's frank?
- Oh, please do.
- [Laughter continues]
Ow! Oh, not so hard!
All right, frank.
Let them have it.
[Muffled]
I'm tom servo,
and I'm a cute little guy
with a round head.
[Laughing]
And I've got these little
adorable arms.
And I'm crow t. Robot,
and I'm gold,
and I'm trapped in space.
What a stupid color gold is.
[Laughing]
Well, I trust you can see
that two can play
at that game, nelson.
Anyway, your experiment
this week
is called the atomic brain.
Plus there's a short
about the golden age
of juvenile delinquency.
[Laughs]
Oh, frank, that's very good.
You've almost got tom down.
Keep flapping those arms.
[Laughs]
Uh, you keep practicing.
I'll get the button.
I'm dr. Clayton forrester,
and I've got my head stuck--
- [alarm blaring]
- The movie's starting!
[All shouting]
- ♪♪ [Dramatic]
- ♪♪ [humming]
- Hey, sam eagle presents--
- hey, it is.
"What about
juvenile delinquency."
That's a viable career option.
Sure. Yep.
Past president disbarred
for delinquency.
And, of course, music by
the royal delinquent orchestra,
philip gannel conductor.
Centron-- the dawning
of a new day.
[Laughs]
The barton millner gang.
Oh, they're so klandinctu.
Here he comes.
- Here's my dad to pick us up.
- [Laughs]
- Come on, guys.
Let's go study.
- Whoo!
- Where are we heading?
- I'll tell you
when we pick up jamie.
In other words, you don't know.
Hmm.
I'm sure glad
we got the car washed.
[Laughs]
Cannonball run.
Well within the speed limit.
- What's that guy waiting for?
- Give him a bump.
Yeah.
- Gordon jump.
- Hit him again.
Aw, cut it out.
We'll get in a jam.
- [Mocking gibberish]
- What's the matter?
You thinking of something?
- Come on! Move it!
- Cars were made
to take it back then.
What do you punks think
you're doing anyway?
Our maytag broke, sir.
What was that you called us?
I just bought that car.
Now look.
He's changing into
the incredible hulk.
When good-natured ribbing
goes too far.
- Hmm.
- ♪♪ [upbeat jazz]
[Gasps]
They flattened him! Oh!
- Oh.
- Whoo.
Oh, willard scott,
I'll gently polish you.
Bzz. Whoo.
I have just enough time
to get into my bo peep outfit.
- ♪♪ [Continues]
- What, does she live
at shakey's?
Oh, mom,
dusting is so bourgeois.
Do you have any homework, jamie?
- And quit playing that ragtime.
- I told you, no.
I'm going out
as soon as the guys come by
and get me.
- Groovin' j.D. Hair.
- What time is it?
- It's already after 8:00.
- Whoo!
I don't know why you can't
stay home for one evening.
- Ma, I can see up your dress.
- Your father will be home
in a little bit.
He should be home now.
Just where is it you're going,
jamie?
- Crack house. Why?
- If I knew, I'd tell you.
- I don't know.
- Don't kill your father.
Well, at least my dress
matches the wallpaper.
Huh?
Ooh, all the dark teens.
♪ Darkness, darkness ♪
[Muttering]
A dry cleaner!
One hour, guys.
Let's martinize.
Use the doors, please.
You start out
not using the doors,
next thing you know,
you're beating up gordon jump.
[All chanting]
Norm! Norm! Norm!
- Norm! Norm!
- [Laughter]
- All right! Bridge club!
- Whoo!
What'll you have, boys?
I'll write your orders
with my new pencil.
Hey, those are great.
My dad's got one just like it.
Where'd you get it?
[Laughs]
Shop 'n save.
We just swarmed all over a guy.
Fell out of his pocket.
- What? When did this happen?
- Just before we picked you up.
We bumped some guy
in a big buick, and he gets out
and starts getting smart.
- Duh, smart, yeah.
- Boy, did we give it to him.
We sure messed him up.
You should've been there, jamie.
- Who was he?
- I don't know.
Some big bald-headed guy.
Do you smell onions?
What kind of a car
did you say it was?
- Oh, it was a--
- uh, the fordillac.
What's the matter with you?
I asked you what kind
of a car it was.
I wanna know.
It was a yellow buick.
Why?
Just trying to draw you out.
You want some fries?
A fisher space pen.
What do you wanna
know for, jamie?
Where's the little
delinquents' room?
Get this thing off me!
[Grunting]
[Huffs]
You're gonna miss
the soup of the day, jerk.
- What's his trouble?
- I don't know,
but this isn't the place
to find out.
- The no shoulder gang.
- We'll see him in the morning
at school
when we give this to him.
We gotta get better patches.
Ooh! Ow!
- Dear, it's just lemon juice.
- Ohh, ow!
- Jamie!
- How's dad?
- How did you know?
- He's always been my dad.
I heard it over the radio.
How is he?
- He'll be all right.
- He's kind of rubbery.
- He's resting now.
- Or he's dead.
It's hard to tell with him.
He was terribly shaken up
and bruised, though.
And they took his pencil pouch.
Oh, it makes me sick
to think about it.
When did his nose
get mildew?
Jamie...
Massage me, will you?
I'm sorry, dad.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I'm not
the daughter you wanted.
It's nothing for you
to be sorry about, son.
Wasn't your fault.
Eh, the next weekend,
dad's golf buddies come
and beat up jamie.
Son, you have angel-hair pasta
on your shirt.
I wonder if this
is gonna get melodramatic.
Okay, come on.
I'll take you both on.
I'm all right now.
You'd better get upstairs
to bed.
- And I'll be up in a minute.
- ♪♪ [dramatic]
- I'm sorry, dad.
- Now, at this point here,
the mood shifts
to a lovely adagio.
- It's fantastic.
- You expecting a flood, son?
It's just upstairs
and to the left, son,
where it always was.
- We're alone. Love me!
- Darling.
Huh.
♪ It's the eye of the t-- ♪
oh, boy.
We brought your tasty shake.
♪♪ [Whistling theme from
the good, the bad and the ugly]
[Imitating sound
of spurs clinking]
[Imitating wolf howling
in distance]
It's a bellboy convention.
- Better take this back, jamie.
- We didn't know
it was your dad, jamie.
- We wouldn't have done it
if we'd known.
- Leave me alone.
- Take it, jamie.
- You keep it.
We're trying to say we're sorry.
I don't want anything more
to do with you.
Now, look, jamie.
Don't get smart.
Don't forget,
you could've been along
instead of one of us.
- Could've been one of our dads.
- Tell you what,
you can beat up my dad.
Wouldn't see me moping around
if it had been my old man.
Don't worry.
I'm not forgetting a thing.
Just count me out from now on.
- [Girl] There he is.
- My backup's here.
- We wanna talk to you.
- He's busy.
- Did you have an appointment?
- Give me a statement.
Have you read about the special
session of the city council
they're having this morning?
And all the things
they're talking about doing--
a curfew, upping the age
of driver's licenses,
canceling the football games,
the parties, the dances,
and everything else.
- And there's witches.
- It isn't fair.
Most of the high school students
haven't had anything to do
with the things
that have been happening.
Like last night,
and the statue that was broken,
and the theater seats,
and all that.
And the suez canal incident.
But we're all going
to suffer for it.
I didn't have anything
to do with it either.
- And don't look at us.
- We didn't kick over
any statues.
- You've got to help us, jamie.
- What do you expect me to do?
[Overlapping shouting]
[Mock crying]
MR. McPHERSON SAID WE COULD GO.
HE EXCUSED US FROM SCHOOL.
And he said
you could go with us.
Look, all of you,
leave me out of everything
you're planning.
- All I wanna do
is mind my own business.
- Yeah, everything.
- But this is your business.
- You heard him.
He's not going anywhere.
He's no sap.
We're going to the city council.
- [Laughter]
- [Mock laughter]
Right now, you guys
are more afraid than we are,
but you're not fooling us.
- You think you can laugh
at anybody who stands up to you.
- Oh!
- Partner, whoo.
- And pretty soon, everyone
else is laughing at him.
- And you think you've won?
- Next card, please.
Thank you.
Well, I don't care
if you laugh or not.
It won't be funny
- ...if the city council does
what they're talking about.
- Whew!
I wouldn't advise any of you
to go to that meeting,
if I were you.
- I'm warning you.
- Are you going with us, jamie?
- No, he's not.
- I'm talking to jamie.
♪ Torn between two peer groups ♪
- What do you want me to do?
- They'll listen to you, jamie,
because it was your dad that...
Awkward.
- Permit me to sing something
from man of la mancha.
- I'll go with you.
- You're not going anywhere.
- [Footsteps]
- Hmm?
- Martha graham! Run!
You boys haven't been moving
the stuff very well.
[Quietly]
I'm watching you.
This is my turf now.
[Laughing]
♪♪ [Imitating mod squad theme]
Pete, linc, julie, and...
- Steve?
- Huh?
Whoa! Banana peel!
- I call shotgun!
- [Laughs]
- No, no, no! Wrong way!
- Whoa!
- Back up.
- There we go.
Eliot ness and his untouchables
were in hot pursuit.
- Get to the helicopter!
The helicopter!
- Get the car!
Meanwhile,
back at the convent...
This is 100% pure democracy.
Okay, everybody,
hurry up and vote! Come on!
♪♪ [Imitating soundtrack]
Whoa. Hold on.
Let me get some literature.
What's the rush?
There's gonna be three hours
of zoning stuff first.
We're not talking about pranks
and letting off steam,
we're talking about
criminal acts for miles!
- We're talking about trouble
right here in river city!
- If these kids wanna go around
beating up people
and wrecking things
to prove how tough they are,
then it's time we prove to them
just how tough we are!
- [Mimicking, gibberish]
- Can we say something?
- I'm sorry--
- what's all this?
Do you have
some facts to give us
that we don't already have?
I don't know whether
you'd call them facts or not,
but, well, everybody
keeps talking about teenagers
as if we were a bunch of freaks
or something.
We're just wasting time.
We've wasted
too much time already.
- KILL THEM ALL!
- WE'VE INVITED
MR. McPHERSON HERE.
He's principal
of the high school.
And he can tell us anything
these kids can tell us.
- No, no. I'm sorry. I can't.
- [Overlapping chatter]
- I'm too noodily.
- That's why when these students
came to me today,
I asked them if they'd
be willing to come down here
and put their case before you.
- Is that okay?
- And I think you should hear
what they have to say.
- I give you cheetah chrome.
- This is bill stillwell,
the head of the student council,
and chuck leewood,
captain of our football team.
- Hut!
- And sally lawrence here,
the senior class president.
- She's a girl.
- And jamie. Jamie's dad was
the one who got hurt last night.
- Mr. Mayor--
- I love you.
...I THINK
MR. McPHERSON'S RIGHT,
and I think these students
are right too.
Teenagers
aren't all delinquents.
- Only a few are involved
- [whispering]
In these criminal acts
that we're all concerned about.
- If these teenagers,
who represent all of the rest--
- [whispering] Hey.
- ...have the courage
to come here,
- [chuckling]
Then I think we should
not only listen to them,
but I think we should--
- obey them!
- ...Invite them to help us
stamp out this vandalism.
I say let's let them talk.
- I say let's put them
through the spanking machine.
- All right.
Whoo, yes.
And tony bouza is introduced.
We don't want to punish
all teenagers
for the trouble
a few are causing--
- just you.
- ...But something
has to be done.
You know how serious
the juvenile delinquency problem
has become.
We have to take some action
to prevent this sort of thing
from happening again.
- Why, he's quite good.
- Now, if you have some
suggestions to offer,
- ...we're willing
to listen to you.
- And then kill you.
What can we do,
and what can you do
to prevent--
- forest fires.
- ...Juvenile delinquency?
- You tell us.
- Yeah?
They called our bluff.
What do we do?
I think they're still talking
about zoning stuff.
I offer myself
as a virgin sacrifice.
[Narrator]
What would you do
if you were jamie?
- That's prince's new name,
isn't it?
- What can we do--
- no, it's frank gorshin's
new name.
- ...About juvenile delinquency?
- What would you say?
- "What would you say?"
- [Laughs]
- ♪ young american ♪
♪ young american,
he was a young american ♪
♪♪ [vocalizing]
Oh, here it is.
[Narrator]
Can death be outwitted?
Like sands
through the hourglass...
Is the secret of eternal life
just around that corner?
Today, medical science
patches up mutilated bodies,
transplanting human skin,
eyes, limbs,
even vital organs.
Golgi apparatus.
Is the next step
the transplantation
of the human brain?
- The pantry of the future.
- Many scientists answer yes,
but they pause
and add a grim warning.
- Oh, hey, we're out of paper.
- For in the ancient
folk legends,
tales are told
of bloodsucking vampires
crawling out of graves
to live in the bodies
of helpless victims.
- But that's another movie.
- Is man now doomed
to produce a race
of ever-living monstrosities--
- huh?
- ...Worse than the vampires
of legend?
- Hey, wait a minute!
- Will ruthless men and women--
- she's nude!
- Lady!
...legally buy or steal
the living bodies
of the young and beautiful
so their brains
may live on forever?
- Such questions
may seem fanciful--
- or downright stupid.
...but at this very moment,
scientists are working
on the answer
to brain transplantation--
- that's not all
they're working on.
- ...And human bodies are used.
But enough about me.
This girl was buried
in a nearby cemetery yesterday.
- That's not a girl.
- Only a few hours ago,
her body was stolen--
now, that's a girl.
...by dr. Otto frank
- ...and brought to
this hidden laboratory.
- Should we be looking at this?
He has grafted
a living animal's brain
into this newly dead body.
- What a knuckle-knob.
- If the experiment works,
the next step will be
the transplantation
of a human brain.
And if it doesn't work,
it's the compost heap.
The brain cells
are being reactivated
by an atomic fission
produced in the cyclotron.
Isn't that a ride
at the state fair?
[Whispers]
Cyclone.
[Imitating liquid bubbling]
And the time's up.
How much have you risked?
All of it? Ooh.
Do not adjust your dryer.
We control your air fluff.
[Chuckling]
Has he found the way
to outwit death?
- Who, durk pearson?
- Or has he created
another monstros--
- what? Another what?
- I missed it.
[Rapping]
♪ I'm a doctor, yeah,
my name is jed ♪
- ♪♪ [beatboxing]
- ♪ I like to wear
this stupid hat ♪
- Huh? Oh.
- You know, guys, people are
just dying to get in there.
- Doh!
- Know how many people
are buried in there?
- All of them!
- [Laughs]
- Thank you.
Looks like joe orton
would meet someone there.
[Chuckles]
Hey, keep it quiet in there.
Hah! Just kidding.
Love that one.
It's barney moonlighting.
♪♪ [Whistling]
[Imitating barney fife]
Yeah, I thought I'd take
thelma lou
over to my pilot
for a picture show.
- Deep below, dr. Frank
takes the chance--
- aah!
...of smashing his way
into a newly sealed vault.
His experiments cannot continue
without another body.
- It's christmas at the vault.
- Oh, nice.
- It's a gary coleman memorial.
- [Laughs]
- Whoa, whoa.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
The watchman's mind
was not on body snatchers--
- starsky and--
- ...Just his usual nip.
[Laughs]
Yeah.
[Imitating guzzling]
- Oh, god,
that's good expectorant.
- Mm.
Well, back to reading
the bridges of madison c--
- what the-- hey.
- ♪♪ [clarinet]
Where the heck is that clarinet
coming from?
Hey, we're, uh, renovating
the crypt here, and...
[Hammering continues]
- Stephen stills!
- [Screams]
That's what he's always
wanted to do to david crosby.
- [Laughing]
- I see.
♪♪ [Flutes]
It's the delightfully
whimsical murder.
- [Laughs]
- Inside the vault,
a body waits.
[Singsong voice]
I'm waiting!
- He's got a coconut head on.
- [Laughs]
♪♪ [Flutes continue]
Galway, rampal.
They're flute police.
Galway, you started the trill
in the upper note!
Someone get a doctor!
Wha-- wait. I am a doctor.
Does it hurt when I do this?
This is one of
the doctor's mistakes--
a monstrosity.
An animal's brain
grafted to a human body.
- In retrospect,
an obvious mistake.
- Leaving the dead watchman,
the monstrosity carried
the girl's body
out of the vault.
It fears and obeys one master:
- Tony orlando.
- ...Dr. Frank.
Enstein.
We gotta get some light
in here, boss.
Someone could get hurt.
- They seem real organized.
- Yeah.
Taxi!
Boss, was I really a mistake
like the man said?
- Oh, no, you were
a little miracle.
- Okay.
And so the little fellow
carted the corpse away.
That's rather a casual look
for a grave robber.
- Nice.
- He probably has espadrilles on
or a nice loafer.
Yeah.
[Tom servo]
Weekend at bernie's:
The armageddon.
Are those my good sheets?
Those are my
300-per-count percales.
Now it's mississippi burning.
[Sighs]
I miss the voice-over guy.
Well, what are you hungry for?
Anyplace
that's got curly fries.
Well, it's a quiet night
here on lake woebegone.
[Whistling]
They're arriving
at jim dine's house.
- Ohh!
- Special dual-action glove box.
Yeah.
No. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
We don't buy this.
♪♪ [Humming addams family theme]
Coming this christmas.
- Selznick international
pictures.
- [Chuckling]
Oh, they're sneaking marilyn
into the white house.
- Ohh!
- Shh!
That car's got bad rings
or something.
Bad pickup.
I don't know.
[Imitating engine sputtering]
Ah, cripes, the warden's up.
Must be watching chevy chase
or something.
Well, I've had
a really nice time tonight.
I hope we can do it
again sometime.
- [Growling]
- Wolfie, honey...
Here beneath the old mansion,
the doctor carefully prepared
for another transplant.
- A pot roast!
- This body had been in
the vault for only a few hours.
Chances seemed better
this time.
Still, dr. Frank was doubtful.
Tissue in dead bodies
deteriorates rapidly.
Where were the live,
fresh bodies
he'd been promised?
Why, straight from
your grocer's freezer.
He bitterly resents
that every step forward
depends on the whim
of a miser, the old woman,
brooding upstairs
in her bedroom.
- [Imitating guzzling]
- Chug it!
Finish it!
All the way!
And hetty march wonders.
Has she been a fool,
squandering money
on this strange experiment?
- [Mock coughing]
- Money hoarded through a long,
greedy lifetime.
Each day, more money.
Each day, death getting closer.
- Ah, but to start life again
in a brand-new body.
- [Coughs] Need a lemon.
- Beautiful and young.
- Kitty.
No price can be
too high for that.
- I'm drunk too. Meow.
- Can she really
trust the doctor?
Can she really trust anyone?
Hasn't everyone tried
to cheat her?
I can't even trust
those blinds.
Wanting her money
while they smiled
at her ugliness.
But they never got a penny.
Oh, how she made them sweat.
- In those satin, tight pants.
- Especially this old fool,
companion and gigolo.
How many years she's kept him
dangling on promises.
Well, sometimes it's convenient
to have a man,
especially when he comes
cheaper than servants.
[Mike]
The strange loves
of martha washington.
The austrian girl?
"Nina rhodes, 18, no family,
pleasing personality."
Whatever that might mean.
Hmph! Thick ankles,
pimply face,
but she always smiles
when she's spoken to.
- Wow.
- Well, application forms
for a servant girl
don't usually include bust,
waist, and hip measurements.
- Except at hooters.
- Ooh.
[Man]
All three will be here tomorrow,
and then you can choose.
[Man on radio]
At green haven cemetery,
the body snatchers
brutally murdered
night watchman robert hanes,
- hey. Shh. This is us.
- ...62, who evidently
interrupted his killers
during their ghoulish task.
His neck was broken.
The imprint
of a huge pair of hands
was found on his throat.
- It's the opinion
of the police--
- god, I hate michael feldman.
- What do ya know? I know this.
- Ring for dr. Frank.
[Buzzes]
So that's what he was doing.
So, then, with just
this little weather kit,
you've transformed
yourself into--
- what was it again?
- Weather servo 9,
first to bring
the satellite of love
vital weather information
that affects you!
♪♪ [humming]
Well, I appreciate that,
but there's very little
weather in space.
And besides, we have instruments
that handle all that.
Servo, you're gonna
die in space.
- Crow! He might not.
- Hey.
That's right, crow.
Now raise weather servo 9
into space,
and I'll report the weather
as it happens to you!
- ♪♪ [Humming]
- Nothing happens to us.
We're protected by a satellite.
I know. Just send
the poor dope out to space.
Don't die!
Up-to-the-minute forecast
from weather servo--
- [hatch closes]
- [Tom servo over radio]
Boy, it's cold out here.
Is it supposed to be this cold?
Aw, don't be afraid.
[Mockingly]
You're weather servo 9.
Servo, just make your report
and then get back in here, okay?
Well, before I
get on with the weather,
I've got a couple of birthdays
to announce.
- [Laughs] I'm just kidding,
of course.
- Oh, boy.
- Man, is it cold out here!
- He's dead meat.
- Yep.
- I guess the big news
is the cold weather.
You might wanna take a jacket.
[Laughs]
It's cold.
Oh, what's this?
Looks like a meteor shower's
gonna be coming by.
It might warm things up a bit.
[Laughs]
[Gasping]
It'll probably pass
just to the north of us,
but you might wanna...
[Screaming]
Servo!
Looks like it's not working.
Cambot, you better show me
rocket number 9.
[Screaming continues]
[Muttering]
Well, that'll happen.
Servo, are you all right?
Servo, buddy,
speak to me.
Well,
[coughs]
I'm not cold anymore.
I better start fixing you up.
- Wow. You look so cool, servo.
- [Sizzles]
- Hey, mike, can I do that?
- No, you cannot do that.
- We'll be right back.
- Weather [coughs] station...
Help.
[Laughs]
Head happens to be on fire.
Might wanna...
[Laughs]
♪♪ [Humming]
[Equipment whirring]
- Hmm.
- ♪♪ [humming]
Hope you're okay.
[Clears throat]
This just in...
Hah! It's jerzy kosinski.
[Chuckling]
[Muttering]
Romper, stomper, bomper boo.
Well, mike, you know,
public access tv
just is not very good.
Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
Mmm.
Whoa.
Hey, there's a naked lady
in this movie,
and she's nude
with no clothes on.
[Whirring continues]
Sounds like the printer's stuck.
Oh, darn!
I need another quarter.
Oh, whenever I put this suit on,
I gotta tinkle.
Oh, I gotta start
those new potatoes.
Ann-margrock.
You know,
jame gumb only dreamed
of achieving
what this guy has.
Oh, who died in here?
[Tom servo]
Point of law.
Miss marple arrives.
[Crow]
Murder, most goofy.
He's got another nudey
on the slab.
More of this hocus-pocus, hetty?
The doctor transplanted
the brain
from a live dog
to a dead human body.
- Can you stand it?
- You saw the creature walk out
of that cylinder alive.
- How many failures since then?
- Oh.
Well, it's your money.
Oh, hi.
Didn't hear the bell.
Okay, can we get a level,
please?
- This specimen is excellent.
- And the police are looking
for the body snatchers.
- Ma, don't hit, please.
- Why the local cemetery,
doctor?
Are you trying
to blaze a trail to our door?
The final test was essential
for your protection.
As for the police,
if they come here,
I hit this switch,
and a nuclear reaction
is set off.
- Oh, well, that ma-- what?
- Close the circuit breaker,
and in a matter of minutes,
this house and any evidence
it might contain
becomes a radioactive hole
in the ground.
- Be careful.
- Is there a way we could live
and still evade the police?
Well, nothing must go wrong.
Jeez, she's the battle-ax
potemkin.
Yeah.
There's no sign of life.
- Yeah? Look who's talking.
- Watch.
What?
I can't wait till I'm her.
Now, don't look at her
chestocological region.
Did I get
really dead last night?
She's sort of alive!
Oh, just radiate
the whole room, please.
The joshua light show.
- She lacks but one thing.
- Big, hunky me.
- A brain.
- Man, he's picky.
Hans was still living
when he was dragged
from that wrecked car.
That's why we succeeded
with the transplant.
Let's see.
What else can I do around here?
- She seems alive.
- She is, to a limited extent.
She'll be able to move around,
but the brain deterioration
is too extensive
for thought processes.
Hey. Hey, don't tease
the corpse.
[Tapping continues]
I am trying to sleep.
♪ Flew in from
miami beach b.O.A.C. ♪
♪ Couldn't get to bed
last night ♪
- ♪♪ [humming]
- The boeing 707,
the pack mule
of the american skies.
Sheep-like passengers
too stupid to appreciate
technologies inherited
from long-range bombers.
Bye, grandma.
Hope you enjoy the sex change.
- Scandinavian airlines.
- I see.
♪♪ [Imitating soundtrack music]
Wilma!
Atomic butt.
[Chuckles]
♪♪ [Upbeat]
Mrs. Wiggins!
♪♪ [All imitating
soundtrack music]
Ooh, this thing needs a rest.
[Foreign accent]
Say, pardon me,
but how far is hollywood
from here?
And could you tell me where
my accent is from?
Come on, come on!
All right. Let's see.
Ooh-hoo!
The schlossen cutoff!
- Ooh-hoo-hoo!
- It's about ten miles.
Which way?
That way.
Hmm? Oh.
[Woman]
Are you going to hollywood?
No such luck.
I'm what's known
as a foreign domestic.
For the next 12 months,
I'll be scrubbing floors
and making beds.
But when my time's up,
hollywood, look out.
- All right. We're warned.
- That's strange.
A foreign domestic agency
paid my passage too.
- I'm from vienna, austria.
- Uh-huh.
- Oh, really?
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm from england.
- No!
- Is this your first trip?
- We have an official bevy.
Yes. I'm awful excited.
- Por favor.
- Yeah! [Laughs]
- PLEASE!
- I NO SPEAK INGLéS VERY GOOD.
You're all from nebraska.
Cut it out.
"Hand over your
wallet promptly."
Well, I better do it.
Your mission, mr. Phelps,
should you decide to accept it,
is to pick up
these three foreign women
at the l.a.
international airport.
- Should you or any of your--
- yeah, yeah.
It goes on like that.
- We know.
- Sorry.
Are you going to work
for mrs. March too?
- YES-- I MEAN, Sí.
- THIS SOUNDS LIKE A SISTER ACT.
- Hmm? "Mrs. Bat guano,"
if it really is your name.
- You too?
- Nina rhodes?
- Yo!
Yes, sir.
Anita gon-- gonzalez?
- Right at ya!
- Kirby puckett!
- Beatrice mullins here?
- That's right.
Are you mr. March?
No. I work for mrs. March.
- Come along.
- It's alexander's ragtime band.
[Narrator]
Three new bodies--
fresh, live, young, bodies.
- This fall on nbc.
- No families or friends
within thousands of miles,
no one to ask
embarrassing questions
when they disappear.
[Mike]
The facts of life
go to europe.
Not that I've seen it.
They're off to a murder
in sunny california.
♪ L.a. is a great big freeway ♪
♪♪ [humming along]
[Narrator]
Victor wondered which one
mrs. March would pick--
the little mexican,
the girl from vienna,
or the buxom blonde.
- Or the...
- Victor knew his pick,
but he still felt uneasy.
Making love
to an 80-year-old woman
in the body
of a 20-year-old girl
is insanity.
- Oh, they do it
every day in l.a.
- still, hetty's plan
to transfer her fortune
to the new body
had been brilliant.
Unpleasant to think about
what's going to happen
to these girls,
but a man has to consider
his own future.
- Hey, you're rationalizing.
- What would happen to him
if hetty were to cast him off
after all these years?
Blanche, no!
[Imitates tires screeching]
[Imitates thudding]
- I am not sharing a room
with beth, am I?
- [Beatrice mutters]
Well, there's your new home,
girls.
The pygmalion sisters.
[Beatrice sighs]
Gives me the shivers.
- Aren't there any neighbors?
- No.
When you get close to an accent,
let us know.
Are there any other servants?
No, but I don't think
you're going to find it boring.
That's three down
and seven to go.
Bennett cerf.
[Gasps]
Trumpy, you can do magic!
♪♪ [Humming]
♪ And there's a rose
in a fisted glove ♪
Mm. Boy, a long day, huh?
I'm just gonna climb into
a nice hot bath.
Yeah.
Clara peller in rear window.
Weird window.
- Whoa-oa-oa-oa!
[Imitating crashing]
- [Laughing]
I'll get it!
Gotta do everything around here.
Meow.
[Sniffs]
You have cats, don't you?
What a jolly little place
this is.
[English accent]
I said "place,"
'cause I'm english.
Dick van dyke had
a better english accent.
Oh, hi. How ya doin'?
- [Screams]
- That's spanish for "aahh!"
Now, hurry along.
Hurry up. Now go.
It's a 20-year
charlie's angels reunion.
Oh, I should've pledged
lambda chi omega.
And this is the room
where president kennedy and I
had the ball
for the spanish ambassador.
The one I had to meet you there.
Oh, they're going to pay
their respects to the pre-dead.
♪♪ [Imitating soundtrack music]
[Elderly female voice]
Norman!
- Oh.
- I know you're looking
at my jewelry.
Put down your luggage.
Tonight on a very special
grandma ironside...
[Imitating wheels squeaking]
Okay, who's bunking with me?
UH, YOU WANNA SEE
MY RESUMé MAYBE?
What are you, mrs. Penguin?
Get that thing away from me.
Turn around.
- Oh, wow.
- Slowly.
Get the doctor.
- Get the doctor!
- I could be the doctor!
I'll be the doctor!
Blimey.
[Knocking]
Hey.
Yeah, let's give somebody else
a crack at that bowl, huh?
Oh, right in the middle
of splicing recombinant dna!
I'm never gonna...
♪♪ [Whistling]
Huh. Messy.
Well, I wouldn't live here.
Well...
Hey, he's got one of those.
Huh.
As with the other bodies
stolen from cemeteries,
the nerve endings of the brain
were too far gone
to receive a proper transplant.
- Well, live and learn.
- The experiment failed
to produce anything more
than a walking, breathing,
zombie-like creature.
- Hey.
- But the doctor permitted her
to wander about the laboratory.
- She was quite harmless
and, at times--
- nude.
- ...even amusing.
- Wow.
[Dr. Frank]
Charming, isn't she?
- Did you want something?
- [Mike] Um, her.
[Victor]
Uh, mrs. March
is waiting for you.
- Three girls have arrived.
- And I'll stay here
and supervise the zombie.
[Victor]
She doesn't have a brain?
She'd make a good news anchor.
[Victor]
Might be advantages.
Oh, thank you, orrin hatch.
The old bat smells like--
oh, hi!
[Chuckles]
I want them examined
immediately.
Very well. This way.
Would you go over
our job description again?
I'm foggy on that.
- Come here. I feel frisky.
- Look here.
The doctor can conduct
the examination perfectly.
[Chuckling]
What an old spoilsport I am.
That woman diapered
rose kennedy.
Have you disconnected
the phone?
Can't I depend on you
for anything?
Won't it be nice
when those girls
start calling police,
employment agencies,
immigration authorities,
counselors?
- There will be no phone calls.
- We have a winner.
Look. Lookit here.
There was a zit,
but I squeezed it.
- Ohh!
- West virginia?
Hideous. She's useless.
There is one more test
I should make.
Do anything you want with her.
- The other two?
- Perfect medical specimens.
- Wow.
- [Whistles]
All right, anita.
Get dressed now
and wait for the others.
- Sí.
- [CREATURE HOWLING]
I'm scared.
♪ So we change partners ♪
- It's maggie the cat auditions.
- Mrs. March, I am now
giving you notice.
I do not care to work
in this house any longer.
- I demand that--
- you have signed an agreement.
If you have any objection,
you will discuss them with
the immigration authorities
as provided for in your papers.
- But, mrs. March--
- later!
Willard scott's gonna
read my name on tv.
Stand up, my dear.
I've got the same measurements
as marilyn monroe.
- [Chuckling]
- [Chuckles]
- See? There's the hickey
from bobby kennedy.
- Yeah.
Raoul wallenberg.
- She had a may-december romance
with eubie blake.
- [Clears throat]
[Laughs]
- The lucky girl?
- Yes.
Allow me to be the first
to offer congratulations.
You've been fondled
by mildred natwick.
- To both of you.
- [Laughs]
I don't get it.
- For me?
- Walls and everything?
Wow! You shouldn't have.
You got me in motel 6. Aw.
- ♪♪ [Bouncy soundtrack music]
- Huh?
- What the--
- there's a xylophone built
in that bed.
- Ow!
- Ooh!
- Doh!
- Ooh, nice recovery.
You two get
the "not as hot as her" suite.
Come on. Come on.
Now listen carefully,
runners-up,
in the event
that the blonde woman
is unable to fulfill her duties
as the old woman's new body,
the first runner-up
will be asked to continue on
in those duties.
Now up to kathie lee.
[Chuckles]
Your room is in the basement,
anita.
Nina, your room is upstairs,
right across from the top
of the stairs.
There's a continental breakfast
at 8:00, and if you
hear screaming, don't listen.
Good night.
I'll have to show you.
HEY, HERVé VILLECHAIZE'S ROOM.
See?
- [Muttering]
- Yeah. Got it.
Oh, this is the door
to the optical track.
[Imitating speaking underwater]
- Impetigo.
- No. I think
you mean "vertigo."
Uh, excuse me.
There's a dog brain
in my toilet.
Escher.
Are you ruth underwood?
[Anita]
I think it will be lonesome
down there.
[Victor]
Nonsense. You'll be all right.
Go on.
[Hocks]
It might smell a little damp,
and don't mind the silverfish.
I'm gonna order
the big-foot bash.
Watson, I'm still here.
Watson, I need you.
This clock doesn't work.
- Ta-da.
- Gracias.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
♪ Just a gigolo ♪
♪♪ [humming]
But you're not using at&t.
Oh, the electromagnet
has been destroyed,
rendering the carbon grains
and transmitter useless.
Poopy.
Mm.
I know.
I'll write for help.
I was right.
It really is lonely down here.
- [Whirring]
- Huh?
The microbrewery thing
is really catching on.
♪ Da-da-da-da ♪
imperial margarine.
[Whirring stops]
All right.
An hour off for renegade,
and then back at it.
♪ It's time we stopped ♪
♪ hey, what's that sound ♪
♪ everybody look
what's goin'-- ♪
Take over, chewie.
- Huh?
- Chewie. Chewbacca.
Completely forgot
what I came up here for.
[Chuckling]
[Knocking on door slowly]
[Tom servo: Deep, slow voice]
Housekeeping.
- ¿QUIéN ES?
- "BIKINIS"?
Hmm?
Did she say "bikinis"?
Who is it?
It's the plumber.
I've come to fix your sink.
[Robots laughing]
Isn't she supposed to be
wearing something tighter
or flimsier or more revealing?
Well, I mean,
that's the preferred route,
- ...but that's
not necessarily--
- well, yeah.
[Screams]
Come on. I can't believe
you've never heard
of a chin puppet.
- No. Not me.
- All right. Well, I'll do
the whole demo for you, okay?
- Of a chin puppet?
- Right. A chin puppet.
Hey, why don't you scramble
around front there,
and I'll do the whole stage show
for you, all right?
- You guys are gonna love this.
- Mike, what are you doing
there, honey?
- Honey? Dear?
- Whoa.
♪ Hey, how are you doing
and what do you know ♪
♪ I'm glad you could be here
to see my show, yeah ♪
- Oh, my god!
- I don't get it.
Why are you upside down?
What's not to get?
I'm a chin puppet.
So, on earth, did you just go
ahead and do this for people?
- Yeah.
- And they laughed?
Well, sure. It's funny.
Hey, you're a great crowd.
- Did you ever go
on a date like that?
- Of course not.
Hey, come on.
You guys wanted to see this.
Get into it.
I know,
but in our wildest dreams,
we never imagined this!
- Come on. It's whimsical.
- It's odd and disturbing, mike.
What would possess
a person to do that?
I just don't understand this.
Apparently you're not suited
to chin puppets.
- Let's just call
the whole thing off.
- [Overlapping chatter]
[Robots laughing]
Now, that's funny!
Look at that!
He's got an upside-down face
on his chin!
- Now I get it. It's hilarious.
- [Laughing continues]
- [Alarm blaring]
- [All shouting]
Gee, you're a heavy little guy.
[Grunts]
- Are you okay?
- That wasn't very nice.
Are you sure
she's not in her room?
Yes.
Victor left
a little while ago.
Maybe she went with him.
[English accent]
Look at those little
no-neck monsters.
She didn't get out of
this prison without permission,
that's for sure.
Yeah.
But she would've said good-bye.
Why should she?
We only met her yesterday.
Oh, right. Why care about
the welfare of others?
I don't blame her
for not wanting to sleep
in the "bicement."
That's british for "basement."
Why, there's a chunk
of creamed spinach here.
It's funny, though.
Mrs. March wouldn't even listen
when I asked to be dismissed.
And then she kissed me
full on the lips.
I don't know why.
What the hell is this?
I mean, it's baked on.
She doesn't even have
any uniforms for us.
What in the world
do you think you're doing?
You told us last night
to clean and polish in here.
But your hands.
That will leave a stain on them.
- Now don't argue. Go in
and wash them immediately.
- Relax.
- Speaking of stained...
- You can put the things away
after nina cleans them.
Oh, jam it, aunt may.
Mrs. March, where is anita?
- Anita? Oh.
- The dead one?
- She accidentally dropped
her brain on the floor.
- She left last night.
I would like to give notice too.
- I will discuss it with you--
- at the staff meeting.
- ...another time.
- ♪♪ [humming]
I would give anything
for that figure.
[Whirring]
Yes, it's disco night
at glam slam.
- Come on down.
- ♪♪ [humming]
- Laserium.
- [Imitating whirring]
A hot tub is not relaxing
with all those lights.
No. Never.
- Hey, gandalf's down there.
- Huh?
- With the smoke rings
and all that.
- Oh, brother.
- This guy.
- [Laughs]
- Well. Yeah.
- I think they're done.
- Nina! Nina!
- Quit listening to that stuff!
Come here this instant!
Oh, if only richard widmark
were here.
- Oh, man.
- I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna get airborne.
100% pure adrenaline.
- Yes, mrs. March?
- Your name isn't nina.
But, mrs. March, she's got
polish all over her hands,
and I'm not doing anything.
I don't want you running
up and down stairs.
Those pretty legs of yours
will get ugly muscles.
- She likes big piano legs
on a woman.
- Send nina to me.
- Who doesn't?
- Yes, ma'am.
[Mrs. March]
I'll be in my room.
♪ Here's cathy who's lived
most everywhere ♪
[Laughs]
[Sighs]
Bea, come with me.
What will we become?
I don't think that's what...
[Imitating stairs creaking]
There. You see?
There are signs of seepage
down here.
I want to show you something.
They keep their christmas
decorations down here.
It's amazing.
Look at all the amenities
that anita got.
Hmm.
Anita wouldn't leave
without taking her clothes.
- Have you seen her clothes?
- I think we'd better
get out of here, fast.
Bea, I'd hate to go
if she's still here.
You'll go now
if you go with "may."
- "May"? Now, who's may?
- I don't understand.
Don't know.
Man, she's bossy.
It's trixie belden and honey.
Here. I wanna show you
the tomatoes they put up
and some watermelon
rind pickles.
Oh, that sounds good.
- This hinge is loose.
- Hmm.
Help me.
♪♪ [Dramatic flourish]
♪♪ [Humming "theme from
mission: Impossible]
♪♪ [Humming]
- Now, where did you get that?
- I found it up there.
Well, put that back.
[High-pitched gibberish]
Oh, cripe.
It's open!
He's the atomic vet.
Huh?
Kitty...
[Mutters]
God, I'm lumpy today.
[Imitating girls whispering,
shushing]
Hmm?
One last experiment before
dr. Frank would be ready.
But this was the most critical
of all the experiments.
For the first time,
the grafting operation
would be performed
on a living human body,
and the brain would come
from the doctor's favorite cat.
Jeez, imagine the size
of the litter box.
- Anita was ready.
- Huh?
Jean shepherd's voice-overs
have gotten weird.
It's the strangest
bed and breakfast
I've ever been to.
[Knock on door]
- It's me, nina.
- Oh.
What about your clothes?
- Never mind. Let's go.
- Here. Get in.
Did I hear someone packing?
I thought packing
would fulfill me,
but now I just feel empty.
Oh.
♪♪ [Oboe]
The oboe represents the tension
as they sneak away.
Casper?
[Chuckles]
♪ Rollin', rollin', rollin' ♪
She's spinning donuts
on the deep pile.
Wow.
Bea, she almost saw us.
Let's wait awhile to make sure
we won't run into her.
[GERMAN ACCENT]
MEIN FüHRER, I CAN WALK!
Ah, ah, aahh!
Dr. Frank, quit leaving
your skateboard on the stairs!
[Imitating body
thudding down stairs]
[To soundtrack music,
mrs. Marsh's theme]
♪ she's old, she's old ♪
♪ she's old, so old, old ♪
Did prokofiev do
the music for this?
- Uh, yes. Ernie prokofiev.
- ♪ look out, she's old ♪
♪ she creaks and pops ♪
Let's follow the whimsical
adventures of granny.
[Laughs]
- ♪♪ [Ladies' theme]
- ♪ they're young ♪
♪ they're scared ♪
♪ young and scared ♪
♪ young ♪
- ♪♪ [mrs. March's theme]
- ♪ she-- she's old ♪
♪ look at how old she is ♪
♪ she creaks,
she's so dang old ♪
[Whispers]
Let's go have
some fish and chips.
- ♪♪ [Ladies' theme]
- ♪ scared ♪
♪ they're young ♪
- I never knew I had a basement.
- ♪♪ [mrs. March's theme]
♪ She's old,
she's in the basement ♪
Let's slide down the bannister.
It's fun.
[Laughs]
- ♪♪ [Ladies' theme]
- ♪ young, scared ♪
♪ young stewardesses ♪
♪ scared ♪
♪ ding ♪
- ♪ young ♪
- ♪ thing ♪
Hey, that lady made sandwiches
for the men working
on the sphinx.
[Laughter]
Oh, heavens.
My pacemaker. Oh, damn.
The snoop nieces.
[Chuckles]
- ♪♪ [Ladies' theme]
- ♪ we're young ♪
♪ young, scared ♪
Aah! Dorothy day!
She's a nice lady.
- ♪♪ [Mrs. March's theme]
- ♪ now come on ♪
♪ let's go upstairs ♪
♪ we're scared, we're young ♪
- Bea!
- A doobie.
This is gonna be
some chase scene.
Mm.
♪ She's old, she's old ♪
♪ she creaks,
she goes ♪
- Bea!
- ♪ upstairs ♪
[Mike]
Bea!
[Whirring]
Ah, good renegade tonight.
Well, back at it.
♪ Dum de-dum de-dum de-dum ♪
Oh. That thing.
Wow.
Oh, I just love
these monday klan meetings.
- Do I smell bacon?
- [Thunderclap]
- See? The lightning
opened the door.
- Hmm.
That's a real complicated
porta-potty, isn't it?
- I wouldn't want one.
- Mm-mm.
Ladies and gentlemen,
miss netherworld!
[Imitating crowd cheering]
Hey, no shoes, no brain,
no service, lady.
Looks like, uh, ultraviolet.
- What, with the frowns and...
- [Chuckles]
[Slowly]
Anyone want anything?
Bea!
I-n-g-o.
- Bea, where are you?
- B-34. Bingo.
Answer me!
♪♪ [Humming]
[Gasps]
Shave and a haircut!
What do we do?
I'm here, mrs. March.
Let's see.
That's my harley key.
Oh, there it is.
[Muttering]
She's locked us in.
Dialogue replacement playhouse.
[Nina]
Open it! I said open it!
- ♪ No, I've got ♪
- mrs. March!
♪ The keys down here ♪
Wait.
Selznick international
presents...
[Chuckles]
That's nice.
I love that one.
Well, it seems our options
are limited.
Are you familiar
with rita mae brown?
Wow.
Here.
Let me adjust your aura.
Errr...
Victor!
Get an intercom.
In a minute.
♪♪ [humming]
- What?
- Well, you took long enough.
- You crumpled old bint.
- The lawyer will see you
in the morning.
I told him you were
going to change your will.
Here.
Careful of this step here!
[Grunts]
[All imitating body
thudding down stairs]
You'll have to check
the basement door.
It broke loose.
Oh, my life is getting
more interesting by the minute.
Talia shire is squeaky fromme.
[Panting]
It's evil here. Run!
Oh, hi.
Your receptionist let us in.
Hi.
You've failed.
Oh, you got one of those, huh?
Oh, meow.
[Chuckles]
Oh, isn't it cute?
Yes, it is.
- [Meows]
- Hello. Yes.
- It's lizz winstead.
- She thinks she's a cat!
And I just bought new furniture!
Nice kitty.
Pick her up by the nape.
- Ew.
- [Snarling]
Great. She's a siamese too.
Clean my litter box.
- [Hisses]
- Oh! Jump-started grandma.
Well, I see you still resent
the way mrs. March treats you.
- I can't say that I blame you.
- [Chuckles]
Kitty's always been
very fond of me. Don't you?
- [Purring]
- Ew, she's got ear mites.
Does she have all the instincts
of a cat?
- With half the calories.
- Watch.
She had her shots?
This mouse has the brain
of newt gingrich. Now eat!
Runners, take your marks.
[Snarling]
Somebody help me!
Oh, god!
- [Snarling continues]
- Ow! Ooh! [Mutters]
[Muffled shouting]
Taste it all.
- She ate it.
- I wanted it.
[Imitating chewing, gulps]
Oh.
- Hey, it's
norma desmond's house.
- Oh.
♪♪ [Flute]
Prelude to the afternoon
of a sexually aroused gas mask.
I don't feel dead.
Actually, I feel pretty good.
I sort of think,
therefore I sort of am.
Divorced,
harassed by creditors.
- Bea.
- Lorna luft gazes
out the window.
- Is that anita?
- The real anita hill?
- Where? Oh, I don't think so.
- Sorry.
I'm looking
for the manos set.
[Imitating grunting]
Going uphill is hard
when you're dead.
[Grunting]
Think she's dead on her feet.
- [Laughing]
- Ohh.
Sorry.
Hmm?
♪ Uh, jump the one you're with,
oh, yeah ♪
[Bea]
Look out!
[Screams]
[Gasps]
Somebody help her!
I'll save you, nell!
- ♪♪ [Humming]
- [Creature growling]
What-- alf, no!
[Laughing]
Alf.
Oh, get the hose! Oh, jeez,
I should've had him fixed.
[Dr. Frank]
Back, hans! Back!
- Hmm?
- Persona.
- Interiors.
- Same thing.
[Growling]
I'm visibly reacting.
[Growling continues]
Come on. Back it up, buddy.
Let's see some I.d.
It's so weird when people
dress up their dogs.
- [Chuckles]
- Hans. Hans!
He's speaking in tongues.
[Laughs]
Hmm, I'd like a dog.
Look at his feet.
He's still a puppy.
- [Mutters]
- ♪ so we change partners ♪
Huh?
Gee, do you think he'll chew
his own head off?
I still think
you should've locked them up.
They're not about
to leave this house
after what they've witnessed.
They know hans is outside there.
Pass the caramelized onions.
[Smacks lips]
So, more blood?
I hope there's no spots
on the wine glasses.
Even if we could get past
that creature outside,
there's still
the electric fence.
- Ooh.
- The phone's dead.
Can't get help that way.
- This is the female papillon.
- Papiette.
- If we could get the car--
- we could go for a drive.
That's it! Victor!
Victor?
He likes me, I guess.
BUT I'M SEEING CLAUS VON BüLOW.
If you could get
the keys from him...
[Whispering gibberish]
- Oh, rochester!
- [Whispers] Aahhh.
- Hey.
- Hello, mary.
I was having
a little nightcap.
And it got out of hand.
Whoa, she's gonna pull
a groin muscle.
Who do you think you are,
pinching me?
Well...
[Laughs]
That magoo.
You've done it again.
Maybe you'd like some company.
Someone like me?
Whoa. How's the tumbler
of scotch?
- Yeah.
- [Whistles]
That's more like it.
Oh, I haven't made love
to a woman with teeth
in so long.
Don't you like me, victor?
Oh, if you were only 80.
[Chuckles, mutters]
Oh, there's nothing like
the feel of a real hip.
Mmm, you taste
like a woolworth's counter.
Wait.
I want you to dress
in lederhosen.
Ohhh.
[Imitating crickets chirping]
Hmm.
Hans is chained.
- Let's go outside.
- Outside?
Let's play some shuffleboard.
I think I'd like that.
And then we can take
a real long time
to write a check somewhere.
♪♪
Oh, god, they're gonna sing!
Mr. and mrs. Bridge.
Was it my rippling gluteals
that did it to you?
[Chuckles]
The job isn't so bad
if you know how to handle it.
Knock back a few,
close my eyes,
and think of england.
[Mrs. Marsh]
Victor! Victor!
Aw, cripes,
miss havisham needs me.
I gotta go service grandma.
Oh!
♪♪ [Humming]
Blimey, I hope I don't
get attacked out here
when I'm all alone,
wearing my spike heels.
Walking through
all this tall grass
would make me
particularly unstable
should anything happen,
like I'm attacked.
I only assume there isn't some
kind of mutilated hell beast
running around
that maybe could
shred me pitilessly.
[Chuckles]
[Growling softly]
Ah, here's something
that can cause me
irreparable damage.
- [Hisses]
- What are you doing up there?
Anita, what's the matter
with you?
Don't you know me?
Anita, listen to me. It's--
[Screaming]
- Well, the heck with you, then.
- [Hisses]
Ooh.
Mm, I wish I was
harry connick's girlfriend.
I'll never get to the pyrenees.
[Hans growling]
I hear william conrad.
I think it's the doberman gang.
- Stella! Woof, woof.
- [Growling continues]
Stella!
Hmm?
Anita!
We got cats.
Stay right there.
Don't move.
I'm coming.
♪♪ [Imitating soundtrack music]
Oh, boy, oh, boy!
I've always wanted a pet.
She's trained,
and she wears my size.
[Laughs]
♪♪ [Upbeat]
♪ There's a girl on the roof,
and she thinks she's a cat ♪
♪ she thinks she's a cat,
but she's not, no, she's not ♪
♪ there's a girl on the roof,
and she thinks she's a cat ♪
♪ but she ain't no cat,
no, she ain't no cat ♪
♪ are you sure, are you sure,
are you sure, are you sure? ♪
- ♪ She is not a cat, you know ♪
- ♪ she is not a cat ♪
♪ she is just from mexico ♪
- ♪ mexico ♪
- ♪ she's not a cat ♪
♪ and that is that ♪
♪ she's not a... ♪
The "cat suite" from carousel.
[Snarling]
Anita, if I call
the fire department again,
they'll start laughing.
Anita.
[Crow]
Where eagles dare.
[Snarling continues]
Hmm? Oh, it's joey ramone!
[Chuckles]
Well, what do you know?
[Nina]
Anita, let me help you.
[Mike]
I know a vet in town.
She's a cat who bites her nails.
[Hisses]
♪♪ [Whistling]
- [Growling]
- ♪♪ [continues]
- That is indigestion.
- Anita, wait.
To catch a cat.
[Snarling]
I'll catch you.
[Chuckles]
I'll catch you. Woof.
[Snorts]
- [Growling]
- Take my hand.
I'm a stranger in paradise.
So, did they put stuffing
around the cat brain
so it wouldn't rattle around
inside her skull?
Gotta go walkies,
for crying out loud! Walkies!
[Growling]
This is no good.
We're on top of the monument.
- ♪♪ [Humming]
- Anita.
- [Hisses]
- Anita!
- [Screams]
- [Chuckles]
And she floats gently
to her death.
- Ah.
- Ew.
Well, so much for the "landing
on your feet" theory.
Ooh, that's a nice bathrobe
she's got there,
with the flower print.
- Lovely.
- [Muttering]
...the human eye.
- Oh, you just pop it in
and see stuff.
- Frank?
Oh, hi.
Uh, I, uh, killed your cat.
I'm sorry.
She's unconscious,
but she'll live.
- No.
- She will live.
- Anita won't. She's dead.
Aw, nuts. Wait here.
Nina, dear,
come along with us now.
It's alexander's ragtime band.
You've had a bad shock.
Get out of here, both of you.
- Well, it's my house.
- She's staying with me.
That's martin balsam up there.
- Hmm?
- I swear.
Whoa, look at her run.
Zoom.
[Imitates car passing by]
Time elapsed.
Just take our word for it.
♪♪ [Humming]
So, how's our little
sandy duncan today, hmm?
Ow.
Why don't you
do something for her?
I've done what I can for now.
Later, an operation
might be possible.
You know, beauty is in
the eye of the beholder-- oh!
I'm preserving the eye.
Let me show you.
- Come over here.
- Jeez, they're fusing species
left and right,
and they can't
give her an eyeball?
- It's a martinizer.
- [Electricity arcing]
The cellular structure's
being kept alive
by these electrical vibrations.
- Cool, huh?
- I use the same principle
in keeping that hand alive.
Eat at joe's. Eat at joe's.
Eat at joe's.
Nina's a very lucky girl.
She's got me for a doctor.
- You think that ironical?
- "Ironical"?
- Let me explain.
- Abc-def-ghi-jkl-mnop-
qrstuv-wxyz.
I'm the only man alive today
capable of restoring
your friend's sight.
And I'm very excited about it.
Dr. Alexis carrel,
who pioneered
the transplanting
of vital human organs--
do you always have to clench
your teeth when you talk?
...kept an animal's heart alive
for many years.
- But I'm boring you.
- For this,
he received the nobel prize.
I got a people's choice award.
And I, who have
so far surpassed his effort--
surely you don't want
to compare yourself
with dr. Carrel?
He was humane.
I, too,
fight to preserve life
and to find the means
to improve the lives
of future generations.
But I kill people.
Your viewpoint
is that narrow, ignorant one
held by
the medical society today,
which forces me to work
in a place like this,
to give in to the whims
of a foolish old woman,
because she can supply me
with the funds I need
to continue my work.
- Wow.
- You think I don't cry?
I cry.
[Moaning]
♪ She's just
a pop-eyed oculist ♪
- Nina?
- Yes, bea?
I-- I can't see. Why--
well, you have a diaper
on your face, dear.
- Something happened.
- Don't think about it now.
"Don't think about it"?
Are you listening?
This is important.
Yes?
We must be ready
if a chance comes.
I remember now.
It was anita.
- What's going on?
- She--
oh, my eye! My eye!
- My eye! [Sobbing]
- Oh, she's got
phyllis diller-itis.
Oh, whoops.
That was window cleaner.
Oh, sorry.
Better leave.
Give this a chance
to take effect.
[Crying]
I'm a doctor.
I'll take care of her.
[IMITATING DR. McCOY
FROM STAR TREK]
JIM.
I'm sure you will
take excellent care of her
until your plans call
for something else.
Or am I to be
the next one, doctor?
Or should I say,
herr doktor?
- A selznick--
- hey. Hey.
Oh.
[Crow]
Greystoke: The destruction
of jared-syn.
- [Laughing]
- There.
- Got all the clothes?
- Yes.
And made my hair appointment?
I took care of everything
on your list
while you were talking
with the lawyer.
- Did you pick up
my candy pants?
- Hair appointment--
monday, 10:00 a.m.,
charles of the ritz--
- [imitating richard nixon]
I am not a crook.
- ...Under nina's name.
♪♪ [Imitates dramatic flourish]
I want nina
to model these later,
after I've rested.
You tell her.
Yeah, fine, mrs. Pynchon.
Do anything for you.
Hmm, not enough vinegar
in the water.
Streaks, hmm.
- They're back.
- With new outfits!
I'll have to leave you now.
Remember, I'm going to try
to get us out of here tonight.
Stay alive,
whatever may occur.
Forget about me.
I won't go.
Well, that'll make it easier.
Bea, don't talk like that.
I've been meaning
to tell you that
the whole movie.
Uh, isn't she wearing
her headband a little low?
- Selznick inter--
- [shushing]
- Mrs. Marsh didn't realize
her new body had--
- [robots] Aah!
...such a satisfactory shape.
Perhaps not as spectacular
as the english girl,
- ...but in excellent taste.
- Wow.
She couldn't help being amused.
The stupid girl was not only
modeling mrs. March's
future wardrobe...
[Mike, robots
chattering quietly]
- It's a movie for me!
- No.
So firm, so nicely rounded
in places men like.
[Magic voice]
Mike?
Crow? Servo?
Where is everybody?
Sure gets lonely
being magic voice.
I wish there was another
disembodied voice around here
I could talk to.
[Film narrator]
Well, sometimes it's convenient
to have a man,
especially when he comes
cheaper than servants.
Hey, you're the voice-over guy
from today's movie.
Tell me, what do you like?
What's your favorite hobby?
Making love
to an 80-year-old woman
in the body
of a 20-year-old girl.
Ew! How could you do that?
She was quite harmless
and, at times, even amusing.
You know, I only met you
a few seconds ago,
but you're really yucky.
I can only imagine
what you think of me.
So firm, so nicely rounded
in places men like.
That's it.
Get lost, loser.
Jeez. From now on,
I'm gonna forget about romance
and just get lost in my work.
Commercial sign in five,
four, three, two--
commercial sign now.
Men!
- ♪♪ [Humming]
- You might have knocked
when you came in, victor.
- I might have, yeah.
- I'm sorry.
Don't stop your style show
on my account.
Does my, uh...
Disturb you?
- Hetty, that's unkind.
- Shut up.
The bloom is definitely
off the rose.
You see, it's hard for a vain,
stupid man to realize
that he holds no attraction
for a lovely young girl.
- Ooh, burn.
- Well, I can see where
it would be--
you're not needed now, victor.
Close the door quietly
when you go out.
I'm not going
to be needed at all.
- Nope.
- That's what you're saying,
isn't it?
- After tomorrow, when--
- victor!
- Sit!
- That's enough!
- Get out!
- Not in front
of the white slave.
It's the way it's going to be
when what?
Uh, when we have the picnic,
which is...
[Chuckles nervously]
Thrown away like an old shoe.
Poor old victor.
[Mrs. March]
Don't ask tiresome questions.
- I could snap your neck.
- That will be enough
for tonight.
I want us both to get some rest.
Try to sleep.
- But, mrs. March--
- that's an order!
Do as I say!
You're gonna put
your brain in me, aren't you?
I just know it.
[Mock grunting]
I should get the larger bottles.
More economical.
Vic, hi.
There's someone
who wants money at the door.
[Slurred]
You're not looking for me,
are you?
Why would a pretty young girl
want to be around an old man?
[Slurred gibberish]
What did you try
to tell mrs. Marsh?
You didn't have to sleep
with the cryptkeeper
every night like me.
So that's what you
planned to do--
get rid of old victor
once you get all that money.
- I'm drunk.
- The only thing is,
of course,
it won't really be you.
What will I do
with a little implant now?
- Oh!
- Victor, please tell me.
- Try to make sense.
- I am telling you.
Tomorrow, you'll be one of
the richest women
in the world.
You're gonna be oprah.
Here's a press release.
It's in the mails now.
To all the major
news syndicates.
"Orphan girl sole heir
to march millions."
- And brain.
- "Nina rhodes is a lucky star."
Well, this is
a terrible press release.
I don't understand.
The next press release
will be:
"March mansion
destroyed by fire.
"Cinderella girl, nina rhodes,
sole survivor."
- Only it won't be you.
- Is this what's known
as singing like a canary?
- Yes.
- It's a pity too.
You're nice the way you are.
I'm drunk!
Please don't let it happen.
You could help me and bea
get away.
Okay. I will.
When you're a rich woman,
you wouldn't forget
an old friend,
a friend who saved your life,
would you?
Uh, give me an example.
- Oh...
- Oh, no. Help me
to the bathroom.
Get out to the car
and stay there.
Victor, bea too.
Bea must come too.
- I'm sober now.
- One minute.
Hey.
- So, mike,
where's the atomic brain?
- I don't know.
Dear heloise,
here's a tip for organizing
your spice rack.
Huh?
Jar lids
screwed onto a lazy susan
will adequately suffice.
Sign this.
Sign the pen?
Hurry.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Don't sign the hand.
Ow!
Oh, my ulcer's acting up.
Oh, oh.
Let's see here.
"Lick me, fat boy."
Hey, wait a minute!
[Foreign accent]
Very interesting.
♪♪ [Harpsichord]
Thelonious.
- Looks like roy scheider.
- [Laughs]
Dear mrs. March,
by the time I read this,
you'll be dead.
I'm going to kill
trevor pinnock!
♪♪ [Continues]
Lord, I know I haven't been
the best gigolo,
but I've been the best gigolo
I know how.
Knit one, purl die!
[Stammers]
Oh, got a needle...
[Muttering]
Oh, that was my favorite
darning needle.
Darn!
HI. I'M DARREN McGAVIN.
Hey, you could do
a chin puppet on him, mike.
- Chin...
- Eat steel, lover boy.
Bea, you've got
to come with me.
No. I won't go.
I don't want to go on
living like this.
By the way, I'm behind you.
I'll get victor to help me,
and we will carry you.
Yeah, well, anyway,
it's so comforting
to have you here.
Thanks for staying.
- [Screams]
- Doh!
No, no. Don't be alarmed.
Just doing my yoga.
[Mrs. March]
Want something
from victor, dear?
- Sit down, my dear.
- Where is she?
I'm afraid you're wearing
yourself out with all this
rushing around.
- Ah.
- I don't like that.
[Nina]
You realize she's mad,
don't you, dr. Frank?
- Relax.
- [Mrs. March] Hurry, doctor.
You've got snotoms.
I'll be ready for you shortly,
mrs. March.
[Mrs. March]
I'll be waiting.
- [Imitating whirring sound]
- Bloop.
Mrs. Partridge.
- I like her.
- Oh. [Mutters]
What are the odds we both
go down with hip pointers
on the same day?
Finally about to happen.
What's about to happen?
You don't know
what it's been like for me,
living with this ugly body
of mine.
- Oh, here comes the diatribe.
- [Sighs]
Knowing that any attention
I received
was not for me
but my money.
- Yeah, and your buns of steel.
- [Crow whispering]
- Well, nobody got any of it.
- [Tom servo whispering]
No.
Well, let's have at it then.
I've never know what it was like
to be loved--
oh, god!
[Sighs]
...for myself alone.
Why did you kill victor,
mrs. March?
- Victor?
- Victor? Which one was he?
Victor was a fool!
Okay. I was just wondering.
I'm a practical woman,
dr. Frank.
Now lop my head off.
A businesswoman.
I've never been
a very practical person.
I suppose that makes me
a fool, too, in your eyes.
- Of course not!
- Relax, mrs. March.
Now, now, now, now,
don't levitate now.
Now, let's make sure there's
a nice big air bubble in here.
- [Gasps]
- Oh, that's good.
It's like I'm kissing god.
Oh, yes. Oh!
You're in good hands.
- She had gizzards in her head.
- [Electricity arcing]
Oh, I got a brain
left over now.
- See? Her cerebellum--
all rusted here.
- Yeah.
- Oh, it's gristly the cat.
- Meow.
- [Arcing continues]
- [Liquid bubbling]
Halfway through this,
I have no idea what I'm doing.
[Imitating liquid bubbling]
So, anyway, nina,
am I boring you?
Just tell me, will you? I...
You know, guys,
I wanna go to egypt.
See the sights.
[Dr. Frank, muffled sounding]
Waking up, are you? Good.
- I wanna talk to you.
- Is he eating a sandwich?
[Imitating chomping sounds]
[Smacks lips]
You signed a paper making victor
your legal guardian.
That's right, isn't it?
- I did sign something,
didn't I?
- Mm-hmm.
- That would probably work
as well for me.
- Stop.
We could stay here.
None of this
would have to be destroyed.
We'd get a couch
and maybe some pictures.
- You're doing better,
aren't you?
- [Meows]
Why don't you try it
on your own?
Oh, why don't you hop down and--
oh, you can't.
I wanna know if mrs. March
didn't intend blowing me up
along with
all the rest of this.
How does that guy
reach his time clock?
He can't even punch in.
[Grunting]
You're a very wealthy woman
now, nina.
But you have a porpoise brain.
What I must decide is
how to keep you
and your friends available
with the least amount
of nuisance to myself.
- I could keep you
under sedation--
- true.
...until your signature
was required.
You make the call.
Or I could replace your brain
with one more amenable.
- You got anything
to say about that?
- Just jump in anytime.
What about mrs. March, doctor?
Mrs. March no longer
has a thing to say.
- She drinks from a bowl.
- Do you, my dear?
She's too busy licking her butt.
Completely recovered, I'd say.
How do you feel?
- [Snarls, hisses]
- Don't patronize me!
I'm mad.
I guess a transplant
would be better.
It won't hurt.
And the price is really not
as bad as you think.
[Electricity arcing]
♪♪ [Whistling]
Dr. Frank had enjoyed
this transplantation--
mrs. March's brain winding up
in the body of a cat.
Hey, voice-over guy,
I'm trying to work.
Poetic justice to think
of autocratic mrs. March
scavenging in back-alley
garbage cans for her dinner.
I think I got another brain
in the storeroom here.
- [Door thuds loudly]
- Huh?
[Yowling softly]
But mrs. March doesn't
take things lying down.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
[Yowling continues]
Huh? The hell--
- In a cameo appearance...
- [Chuckles]
Now, see, this is why
I don't like cats.
[Laughs]
They'll blow up
a nuclear pile on you.
Please, no--
you forgot the fabric softener.
- [Door rattling]
- [Coughing]
More milk every night.
Tuna. Lots of tuna.
Come on. Come on.
[Pounding on door]
♪♪ [Whistling]
He's just in a machine shed.
I'll shrink if I'm dried! Oh!
Whoa. Nina, you run into
the bed there?
You all right? Nina? Nina?
Ooh-aah!
[Laughs]
Yabba-dabba-doo.
Kick me.
Okay, okay. My impression
of the scales of justice lady.
Where are my scales? Thank you.
I'm the scales of justice lady.
- Whoa! Was she hit
by a meteorite?
- Whoa.
[Electricity continues arcing]
- Oh, that's what happens when
you drink in a hot tub, folks.
- Yep, yep.
Oh! Oh!
Radiation on an open sore.
Just like lemon juice.
Oh, well,
thanks for rescuing me.
But you could put a sheet
over that thing. Ew.
♪♪ [Imitating dramatic
soundtrack music]
You've got just enough time
to change your pumps.
They're all wrong.
Oh, you know,
as long as I'm here,
I'm gonna grab my eye. Ooh!
[Cries out]
- ♪♪ [Humming]
- [Rumbling]
♪ Joshua fit the battle
of jericho ♪
- ♪ jericho ♪
- ♪♪ [humming]
- [Growling]
- ♪ it's my heart
that's a-sufferin' ♪
Ew, he drooled.
Ehh. What a day.
Now she'll step into a rattrap,
get hit by lightning,
meet the hudson brothers.
[Laughs]
Well, there goes that thing.
Oh, no. Tara.
Mrs. March did not intend
to let her money
get out of sight.
She would follow that girl.
Sometime, someplace,
revenge would come.
But that's the subject
of the sequel.
It's in development right now,
and we've got to do
a memo and...
I suggest
they placate the old woman
with a little fancy feast.
- [Tom servo shouting in german]
- [Mike shouts]
[Imitating gunfire]
[Mike]
The 400 blows.
[Yowls]
Please let me die.
Oh, shame on you,
joseph mascellli.
Bad director! Bad!
[Grunting]
The 7:00 news.
Jack pollexfen.
Yes, mrs. Dwiggins.
[Chuckles]
End the movie, mrs. Dwiggins.
Oh, he came up with...
♪♪ [humming part
of soundtrack music]
♪♪ [Robots join in]
Fine. Fine.
No use calling attention
to yourself.
Jeez.
♪♪ [Humming soundtrack music]
I'm gonna be charitable
and just say
I hope all these people
were forced to do this movie
at gunpoint.
No, they chose to do this movie.
All except for xerxes the cat.
You know, xerxes went on to
a long and extinguished career.
He was a favorite
of nicholas ray's,
and then he appears
courtesy of david o. Selznick...
- ♪♪ [Mike singing]
- Mike! Mike!
Mi-mi-mi-mike!
[Trills]
- Mike, mike, mike.
- Yes, eleanor?
- Ready?
- I was born ready.
Oh, okay.
Oh, kaloo kalay.
- Okay, tom, hit it.
- Ready.
[Clears throat]
Dr. Richard kimble
is a fugitive
on the run from the law.
But in another part
of the world,
green acres' hank kimball
is also on the run from the law.
♪♪ [Humming]
Ah, oh, uh, mr. Nelson,
uh, I'm on the run.
Well, uh, not actually
on the run.
I'm, uh, being pursued,
and I'm walking quickly.
You see,
I'm in flight from the law.
Well, not the whole law.
Uh, actually,
just parts of the law.
When I say "parts,"
I should really say "men."
Not to say there aren't women
in the police force.
There are some women.
I'm just not sure
of the ratio.
I'm also being followed
by a one-armed man,
or a man with a prosthetic arm.
I'm sure he had two arms
when he was born.
Well, thanks very much.
Good night.
- ♪♪ [Humming]
- Boy! Mm!
- Crow buddy--
- wow.
...you set a stool down
next to that premise
and just milked it
for everything it was worth.
- Moo.
- Well, thank you very much.
- Good job.
- Oh.
Okay.
We got a bunch of letters.
- Letters. Oh, I love letters.
- Delicious letters.
And, uh-- well,
let's start with this one here.
This first one's
from eric halloran.
- Put that up on
still store there, cambot.
- Hi, eric.
Eric says,
"dear satellite of love"--
- which is a good start--
"I'm a 13-year-old boy, and"--
- [muttering]
- Please. It's annoying.
- Sorry.
Every time I read the paper--
"I'm writing to say
"I really enjoy the show,
and I really think
it's a laugh riot.
- [Laughs]
- I'm also writing
to ask a question." Here we go.
- Okay.
- "What does the 'k' stand for
in mst3k"?
Uh, I got this one, mike.
[Clears throat]
Eric, the "k" stands for karl.
Karl was the man
who invented lightning.
- Thank you very much.
- Lightning?
- Yeah. Karl.
- Good answer.
All right.
Well, let's move on here.
- Okay.
- This one's kind
of a special, uh--
- check this out. "Just a letter
to let you know"--
- let me see.
This one's from anne feldstein,
by the way.
- Why don't you put that up?
- Hi, anne.
Anne, thank you for writing.
"Just a letter
to let you guys know
- ...how much
I love your show"--
- thank you.
..."and how I especially love
tommy-gun servo."
- Wow.
- "He is my favorite,
and I love his songs.
"If I could be
on the satellite of love,
I would sit and talk to tom
all day long."
- Oh, anne. Oh, sweet anne.
- "Devotedly, anne feldstein."
- Smell it.
- Who's that from?
- Uh, anne feldstein.
- Oh, yeah.
- Feldstein. Yeah. Yeah.
- Anne...
I got a big stack of letters
from feldstein
down in my locker.
- What?
- That's right.
I got a bunch from her too.
Finally got around
to writing you, huh?
Well, you trollop,
you tart, anne.
[Laughs]
- Hey.
- That's anne.
- I'm sorry.
Just a little bitter here.
- We're just kidding.
- Uh, if we can continue on
here, please?
- Please do.
- This is from eric hansen.
- Eric?
- Another eric.
Hansen, halloran.
I smell a conspiracy.
Anyway, put that letter up.
- Neat.
- And I'll show you
a picture too.
"Dear lords of lunar laughter"--
[laughing]
That's us.
"I AM ONE OF THE MILLIONS
OF FANS, OR MSTies,
"who are forced to pump
mst3k into their veins.
"So addicted am I
that I have constructed
a robot companion
"to assist me in alleviating
the tribulations
of bad cinematography.
"My robot,
or more accurately, puppet,
pictured here with me
is a replica of tv's
wisecracking crow
built out of household gadgets."
And let's put
the picture up there.
- Look at that!
- Now. That's very flattering.
But it should be good,
because if you'll notice,
that's not eric at all,
that's george lucas--
- wow!
- What?
...thx developer.
Lookit. You can even see
the graying temples at the side.
- How about that?
- He just shaved his beard
and tried to fool us.
- Aw, george.
- No good, george lucas.
- Thank you.
- That's from eric, anyway.
- Clever, huh?
- Hey, why don't you do
the address for the info club?
Okay. Send your tinctures
and other missives to--
- letters.
- The mystery science theater
information club.
Post office box 5325,
hopkins, minnesota, 55343.
- Do it today.
- Well, I guess that's it.
What do you think, mad guys?
I'm dr. Frank, physician
and bon vivant.
[Chuckling]
[Dr. Forrester]
Oh, dr. Frank,
there's a dr. Fist
here to see you.
Well, send him right in--
hey, wait. I'm not gonna fall
for that one again.
He really wants
to consult with you, dr. Frank.
He says it's very important.
Important? Consult?
Well, I am a doctor after all.
Send him right in.
Come in.
[Chuckles]
Well, hello, dr. Fist.
Tell me, what is your-- oh!
Sometimes it's just too easy.
[Screams]